https://www.crouse.org/privacy-policy/

Central New York Support Groups
Inside CrouseMission, Vision and Values Crouse Health Leadership
Corporate Compliance Diversity and Inclusion
Crouse History Healing Environment
Back to About CrouseCrouse Health LeadershipSenior Leadership Medical Staff Leadership Board of Directors
Back to Inside CrouseDiversity and InclusionOverview and News Diversity & Inclusion Leadership
Back to Inside CrouseQuality at CrousePatient Feedback Crouse Stories Quality Initiatives Crouse Germinators Quality Partners Choosing a Hospital Quality Employees Speak Up Resources Quality Awards and Designations Contact Us
Back to About CrouseIn the CommunityWellness-Outreach Programs Educational Partnerships Community Partnerships Financial Summary of Community Benefits/Charity Care
Back to About Crouse
Services
Services
Addiction Treatment Services
Breast Health Center
Cancer Care
Cardiology
Care Coordination Services
Crouse Testing Center
Emergency Services
Hospitalists
Imaging Services
Integrative Medicine
Maternity/Kienzle Family Maternity Center
Neonatal Intensive Care Unit (NICU)
Neuroscience Institute
Orthopedic Care
Palliative Medicine
Patient and Guest Relations
Physical Rehabilitation
Robotic Surgery
Spiritual Care
Surgical Services
Weight Loss Surgery
Urology
Women's Services
Addiction Treatment ServicesAbout Us Programs Special Populations Fetal Alcohol Spectrum Disorders Additional Services Contact Information and Directions
Back to ServicesBreast Health CenterMake an Appointment Location/Hours Breast Imaging All Mammograms Are Not Equal Breast Cancer Resources Breast Care Partners Our Multi-Specialty Breast Healthcare Team
Back to ServicesCancer CareTeam Approach Infusion Services Kelly's Comfort Zone
Back to ServicesCardiologyCardiology with Carepassion Heart Emergencies Adult Cardiology Providers Pediatric Cardiology Providers Cardiac Catheterization Lab Electrophysiology Lab Echocardiology Lab Cardiology Devices Request a Cardiology Appointment
Back to ServicesEmergency ServicesNew Pomeroy Emergency Services Department Minutes Matter Your Emergency Visit Emergency Preparedness
Back to ServicesEmergency PreparednessPrepare Yourself Safety and First Aid Emergency Events Natural Emergencies Major Trauma Flu Advisory
Back to Emergency ServicesHospitalistsHospitalist Service Our Team Contact Us
Back to ServicesImaging ServicesLung Screening Program Appropriate Use Criteria for Advanced Medical Imaging Imaging Tests Locations and Hours Scheduling Your Imaging Visit Staff
Back to ServicesIntegrative MedicineEducational Programs Patient Programs IM Modalities Integrative Health Alliance Resources
Back to ServicesMaternity/Kienzle Family Maternity CenterAbout Us Delivering at Crouse In-Hospital Midwifery Services First Steps Classes Services Crouse Babies CNY Regional Perinatal Program
Free Perinatal Family Support Group
Cord Blood Donations Contact Us/Directions Resources
Back to ServicesCNY Regional Perinatal ProgramBereaved Families Support Group Personalized Memory Blocks
Back to Maternity/Kienzle Family Maternity CenterFree Perinatal Family Support GroupPerinatal Family Support Group Questionnaire
Back to Maternity/Kienzle Family Maternity CenterNeonatal Intensive Care Unit (NICU)About Us Visiting the NICU For Parents NICU Medical Services NICU Support Services Financial Information
Back to ServicesNeuroscience InstitutePhysician Specialists Technology Neurovascular Neurosurgery Skull Base & Brain Stem Tumors Brain Surgery Spine Care Neurology Comprehensive Stroke Center Contact Us
Back to ServicesOrthopedic CareOrthopedic Surgeons Procedures and Treatment Options Hip Today. Home Tomorrow. Foot and Ankle Patient Orthopedic Videos Understanding Your Joint Replacement Procedure
Back to ServicesPalliative MedicinePatient and Family Care Comfort with Life Quality Consultation Palliative Medicine Team Standards and Guidelines of Practice Resources
Back to ServicesPatient and Guest RelationsContact Us
Back to ServicesPhysical RehabilitationTMJ Disorder Rehabilitation Locations Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation Neurological Therapy Program Pelvic Floor Rehabilitation SMART EquiTest Balance Testing
Back to ServicesRobotic SurgeryRobotic Surgery Team
Back to ServicesSurgical ServicesYour Surgery Colorectal Surgery Surgical Nocturnists Surgical Centers Sinus Surgery
Back to ServicesSinus SurgeryMeet Our Doctors Balloon Sinuplasty Sinusitis
Back to Surgical ServicesWeight Loss SurgeryAbout Weight Loss Surgery Check Your BMI Weight Loss Surgery Info Seminar Lost and Found Weight Loss Surgery Video & Quiz Meet Our Team Weight Loss Ongoing Support Group Patient Information Contact Us
Back to ServicesUrologyPelvic Health Partnership
Services Meet Our Urologists Kidney & Urinary Issues Urologic Cancers Men's Health
Back to ServicesPelvic Health PartnershipPelvic Health Education Meet Our Pelvic Health Providers
Back to Urology
Find a Doctor
Your Visit
Your Visit
For Patients
For Visitors
For PatientsCrouse Cares Patient Rights & Responsibilities Patient Complaints Preparing for Admission Preparing for Surgery Being an Inpatient
Room Service Dining MedEx Bedside Prescription Delivery Medical Records Request Billing and Insurance Hospital Prices Financial Assistance Program
Back to Your VisitBeing an InpatientAccommodations Pain Management Care Coordination
Back to For PatientsFor VisitorsVisitor Responsibilities Visiting Hours and Information Hospital Resources Local Resources Crouse Cares
Back to Your Visit
Your Health
Ways to Give
Ways to Give
Donate Now
Crouse Health Foundation
Crouse Hospital Auxiliary
Volunteer Services
Crouse Health FoundationFoundation Board Foundation Staff Publications Giving to Crouse
Special Events
Contact Us
Back to Ways to GiveGiving to CrouseLittle Fighters
Crouse Cares Campaign
Grateful Patient Program Milestones & Memories Crouse Health Society Caduceus Circle Planned Giving Endowment Fund
Back to Crouse Health FoundationLittle FightersLittle Fighters Features Little Fighter Stories Donate Now Share Your Little Fighters Story
Back to Giving to CrouseCrouse Cares CampaignRegional NICU Project
Back to Giving to CrouseSpecial EventsCrouse Spirit of Women Outing Crouse Health Tribute Evening Crouse Classic Golf Tournament Crouse Health Polo for Preemies
Back to Crouse Health FoundationCrouse Hospital AuxiliaryLights of Love Board Leadership Fundraising & Projects Join Us Contact Us
Back to Ways to GiveVolunteer ServicesGet Involved Volunteer Positions Volunteer Programs Volunteer Application Contact Us
Back to Ways to Give
Contact Us
Important Phone Numbers
Your Crouse Carepassion Story
Contact Us
Directions
Hospital Parking
Crouse Locations
Additional ResourcesCrouse Library
Additional ResourcesAdvance Directives Additional ResourcesSupport Groups Additional ResourcesOrgan and Tissue Donation
Back to Privacy PolicyCrouse LibraryMeet Our Staff Crouse LibraryAsk a Librarian Crouse LibraryOther Resources
Back to Privacy Policy
Pay Hospital Bill
Pay Hospital Bill
Additional ResourcesCrouse Library
Additional ResourcesAdvance Directives Additional ResourcesSupport Groups Additional ResourcesOrgan and Tissue Donation
Back to Privacy PolicyCrouse LibraryMeet Our Staff Crouse LibraryAsk a Librarian Crouse LibraryOther Resources
Back to Privacy Policy
Careers at Crouse
Prospective Employees
New Employees
Current Employees
Search Job Openings
Careers at Crouse
Prospective EmployeesOpportunities at Crouse Prospective EmployeesLive, Work, Play Prospective EmployeesBenefits
Back to Careers at CrouseNew EmployeesBenefits New EmployeesNew Employee Paperwork
Back to Careers at CrouseCurrent EmployeesBenefits Current EmployeesPayroll Forms Current EmployeesSimply Well
Back to Careers at CrouseSearch Job OpeningsSearch all positions Search Job OpeningsSearch nursing positions
Back to Careers at Crouse
College of Nursing
Spirit of Women
Home » Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
Crouse Hospital’s web site is intended to provide information about our programs and services as well as general health-related information. It is not intended to be the source of specific healthcare advice.
All visitors to this site are advised to consult with their own physician regarding their specific healthcare questions and concerns, and to discuss any information provided through this site with their physician before taking any action with regard to their own healthcare needs.
Your Privacy
Crouse Hospital respects the privacy of our users. By accessing our web site and entering information into any of our form pages, you are agreeing to and accepting this Privacy Policy as well as the terms and conditions or other end-user agreements for our site.
We will not distribute information that identifies you individually or reveals your identity (“identifying information”) to any organization outside of the Crouse Hospital network.
We will not make identifying information available publicly without the prior written or electronic consent of the individual identified.
We may collect and use information about you and your use of the Crouse site, including identifying information, for our own internal purposes such as analyzing usage of the web site for improvement purposes.
Crouse Hospital may send users, via email or other means, information relating to our site and/or information on special events, new programs or services and/or promotions from our partners/colleagues. The information described in these messages is intended to be of high interest or value to our users. To choose not to receive such messages, or any other future emails simply choose “no” to receive future Crouse mailings on our form page(s), otherwise your electronic approval will qualify as your consent for this purpose.
If you make a purchase by credit card or otherwise provide your credit card information, the relevant data will be transmitted to Crouse’s vendor providing such payment processing service.
Crouse Hospital may use other companies/outside agencies to perform certain functions for us. These functions might include, for example, processing credit card payments, providing customer service and sending email. These other companies/outside agencies may have access to customer information (such as identifying information) needed to perform their functions, but they are not authorized to use it for any other purposes. In addition, we may share information with other affiliated companies and joint ventures, for example, but we ask those companies to honor the standards of this Privacy Policy.
In order to provide our users with a more complete understanding of how the Crouse Hospital web site collects and uses information from our users, we have provided the following information:
Internet Protocol (IP) Address
The Crouse site may log IP addresses for systems administration, diagnostic, and site tracking purposes. The Crouse site does not link IP addresses to information identifying users individually.
Cookies
The Crouse site may use files called “cookies” to store usernames, passwords and other user preferences so that users don’t have to re-enter this information each time they use our site.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
This privacy policy is subject to modification from time to time. You may be notified: (1) in an email sent to the email address if you have provided one to Crouse through our site, or (2) Crouse’s posting of a notice for at least 30 days on this web site stating that the privacy policy has been changed.
Crouse Hospital’s full privacy policy can be accessed here. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact us.
